What do you think?
Did it work?
Do I...
Do I look like Shizuku-tan?
Yes!
You really do!
You're the perfect Shizuku-tan!
You're right!
I am!
I can feel it!
Thank you, Gojo!
I'm totally Shizuku-tan right now!
You are!
You're totally Shizuku-tan!
But how does it fit you?
Does it feel too tight anywhere?
No, it's perfect!
Well, I guess maybe a little here.
Like, I can't extend my arm much.
But who needs straight arms?
Oh, right.
Making clothes for humans means I have to consider comfort and mobility.
But you nailed the important part!
I didn't know these boob bag things could look so realistic!
I mean, check out the bounce factor!
Dang!
These babies are O-P-A-F!
And this skirt is, like, the perfect length!
I mean, you just get her!
Shizuku-tan is all about the low-key yet screaming garter reveal.
And you crush that!
Like, show me to your temple!
Well, thank you, that's really nice.
I'm so flattered I don't know what else to say.
But I do still have a long way to go.
I can't believe this is my life right now!
Like, I'm finally Shizuku-tan for real!
Am I dreaming?
Pinch me!
No, wait, don't!
Like, what?!
I never thought this would actually happen for me!
I can't even!
I can't!
I'm so excited I'm gonna explode!
Okay, Kitagawa, calm down.
I need photos!
Wanna take pics for me, please?
Uh, okay.
Let's see.
Yeah, that looks good.
Oh my god, did you get it?
Is it fierce?
I wanna see, too!
Sweet!
Yeah, it's a good picture, for sure.
But you're just kinda posing like you.
And what's wrong with that?
I'm hilarious, get used to it.
Okay, but since you're cosplaying and all,
maybe you should pose more like your character would.
And this background's not quite right.
We should go and take these somewhere
that looks more like Shizuku-tan's world.
Oh, I feel that.
How about over here?
Huh?
This is neutral enough to be anywhere.
Okay, you're Shizuku-tan now.
Let's see it.
Yes, sir!
Oh, crap, I cheesed!
Nope, sorry!
Can't stop, won't stop, must smile!
How can I not?
I'm so happy I could just die!
Don't hate me!
I promise I'll do it right and be super serious!
Please take it one more time!
Okay.
I got this.
So serious.
Is it all right?
Did we get it?
Sure did!
That one was incredible!
For real?
Yes!
Let's keep going while you're on a roll!
Okay!
Looking good!
You've got our poses down perfectly!
Oh, wow!
Yeah, that looks awesome!
You are Shizuku-tan!
Okay, now look right at the camera.
That face!
It's just like that scene where she's with the main guy!
It's amazing!
Do you think that's enough?
We caught a lot.
Cool, thanks!
Can I see them?
Wow, Gojo, these look fab!
I'm so psyched now!
I'm gonna create an account and upload these right away!
You already want to post them?
Duh!
Except I haven't thought of a cosplay name yet.
Hmm.
Ma.
Mar.
I guess we can go with Marine.
I can't get over how cute these pics are!
Like I can't, Gojo!
Ah.
Hey, you know what?
Hm?
What's up?
I think we should go to the event tomorrow.
Huh?
I'm ready now, so why not?
Come on!
It'll be fun!
X10
東日本
北日本
See you next time.
I don't know, man.
This is a dream come true. It's finally happening. My cosplay debut. I've never been happier in my entire life. I really don't know how to thank you.
Oh, holy sweat beads. Are you okay?
Hey.
And if they are staring, it's probably because this is the best boom bag here. No one else's even comes close and they're jealous.
Okay, I get it. But do you have to do that out here?
We don't have to hang here if it's making you nervous. I saw some photographers and other dudes in the plaza. We can go there.
Cool. I'm sorry.
Wow! It's like a super chill oasis. Nice.
Definitely not as bad up here.
Ooh, check out that Vanessa over there. She's so cute. Her rack is ginormous, too. I'm gonna line up to get a pic with her for sure.
Excuse me? You mind if I take some pictures?
Huh? Wait, are you talking to me?
Uh, yeah. You're Shizuku Kuroi from Slippery Girls 2, right?
Ah! Yes! Shizuku Tana rules!
Yeah! Oh, but it's cool if you don't do photos.
What? No, I'm totally fine with it. In fact, that sounds awesome.
Perfect! I really appreciate it.
Can you do a posing character?
Of course!
Oh, whoa! That's super cute!
It is! Thank you so much!
Are you kidding? I appreciate it. Hold on, I have an idea. Let's take a photo together, cool?
Savor the memory!
Okay, here we go.
Hey, you can come closer if you want. I'm not gonna bite you.
Oh, yeah. Sorry.
Thank you so much, dude. You totes made my day.
Hi, you look great. Could I get some photos, too?
Yeah, of course you can. Thanks.
She's got a line. Amazing.
Could you give me a pose, please?
Okay.
Okay, good. I'm glad she's posing like she's a Grinnell.
Yeah, thanks.
People cosplay in drag, too?
Now that I think about it, I guess there were a lot of girls dressed as guy characters downstairs.
I get it.
They're cosplaying their favorite character no matter who it is.
That's what makes it so much fun for them.
This is really nice.
She looks happy.
I'm glad she's having a good time.
And that I could keep my promise to her.
Oh.
I beg you.
Please help me make the perfect cosplay.
Oh.
That's right.
I did what she asked me to do.
So I won't get to hang out with Kitagawa like this anymore.
Looks like today's the last day.
I'm glad I met her.
Not having friends and always doing everything alone made talking to someone like her really special.
Going shopping with a friend?
Actually having plans after school?
Meeting up on our days off?
Spending my free time with someone else?
Well, those were firsts for me.
Thinking about it, it almost doesn't seem real.
It was so much fun.
I'll tell you.
Good night.
Oh.
Oh, my God.
Um, hey, are you okay?
You're still here.
Huh? Yeah!
Thank goodness.
I thought you decided to dip without me and totally freaked out.
So, real talk.
I think...
My clothes are gonna come off!
I'm sorry, what?
They're coming off?
Which part's not working for you?
Well, here's the thing.
Last night, I was looking at the pics you took of me in the outfit.
Hold on.
Aren't Shizukatan's boobs way bigger than that?
So, this morning, I added some special bras to give me a little extra lift, you know?
And I feel like I'm about to burst.
Yeah, you probably are!
That outfit was measured in sewn to fit you perfectly.
There isn't room for special bras or whatever.
You don't have to match the exact chest size of a game character.
Okay, but it's also Sweaty Stanktown under this wig.
The whole outfit is just a furnace.
I'm gonna die.
Like, for real.
Oh, no!
This must be because I picked the thicker fabric!
I'm so sorry!
This is all my fault!
Let's go somewhere you can cool off!
So good.
Gojo, you, sir, are a lifesaver.
I'm glad.
Do you think you can make it to the changing room?
No way!
I can't move.
I wish I'd thought more about how hot it would be.
I really am sorry.
Oh, thanks!
So much!
You should also cool off your neck, Sun.
And your underarms and anywhere with a major artery.
Okay.
Here's a towel.
Use it to wipe your sweat.
Will do.
Yuck.
Look how much sweat's up in there.
I don't think I even sweat this much in P.E.
The black fabric definitely makes it worse.
Those special bras are hardcore.
Okay!
Let me see what else we can do to help here.
Yeah, thanks.
Heatstroke is no joke, and I don't want to be lame and pass out.
Okay, I found some... thing.
That's it?
You just gonna stand there and watch me die?
Whoa!
Okay, my dude.
I didn't say rip it off me.
Sit down.
Just unzip it a little.
Can we at least get you to the dressing room?
Huh?
Right.
I'm an idiot.
She said she can't move.
She does seem to be having a rough time.
Here goes.
This is no time to be panicking.
Please excuse me.
Oh!
Holy crap!
Now I'm freezing because my back is dripping wet.
Ugh!
Even my undies are drenched in sweat.
I seriously should have brought an extra pair.
Next time.
Hey, Gojo?
Could you wipe my back?
Uh, sure.
Stop panicking, dude!
Okay.
So, I'm gonna wipe now.
Ugh!
Whoa!
Could you go a little lower?
I'm like a fountain, I swear.
L-lower?
You mean like...
here?
Yeah, there.
Right there.
Yes!
Oh, that feels so good!
Oh, wow.
Yeah!
Ah!
There!
More!
Hey, Kitagawa, can you try to keep your voice down, please?
Someone's gonna hear you and come back here.
No, they won't!
Besides, I'm not being that loud, and if I am, I'm not trying to, so whatever.
Oh, yeah.
I'm pretty sure that I've got a swamp under here.
Gojo, could you hand me a towel?
Put that down!
Someone might see!
Don't you worry about that.
I've got shorts on!
You do?
Oh, of course you do!
Those look neat.
Did you write them out yourself?
I did!
I figured if I want to be Shizuku-tan, I should probably go all out.
Huh, yeah, that's cool.
Okay, this should help to reinforce it.
You're the best.
Be careful, though.
It's not as strong as a sewing machine stitch.
Mm-hmm.
I think we should head home for now.
Good idea.
You seem pretty exhausted.
I'm so sorry, Gojo.
Could we go back to the plaza again?
It'll only take a second.
Oh, hey there!
Shizuku, you're back!
Sorry for running off like that earlier.
I got dizzy from all this heat.
What?
That's terrible.
I'm so sorry.
I'm actually feeling much better now when heading home,
but I felt awful for bailing on you earlier.
So I wanted to finish the shoot.
Oh, you didn't have to do that.
But if you don't mind, I'd love a shot in the shade.
Maybe over here.
Of course!
Here we go.
Last photo of the day.
Could I get you to look at the camera, please?
Oh, crap.
I'm sorry!
I don't know what I was thinking.
I'm deleting them now.
Oh, I don't blame you.
You're right.
I wasn't looking at the camera at all.
Sorry.
What?
Okay, one more.
This time, I'll get it right.
That's what she's worried about?
I'm glad we found a seat.
Yeah, we're lucky it isn't crowded.
Thanks, Gojo.
Great job today.
Man, I guess that means summer's here already.
Looks like.
I can't wait to jump into the shower as soon as I get home.
Kitagawa?
Huh?
Thank you for everything.
I know it was rough at times,
but this was a great experience.
And I...
I really had fun with you.
I did too.
So much fun with you.
Thanks, Gojo.
You rule.
So what are we gonna do for the next one?
Next one?
My next cosplay.
Huh?
Uh, so...
You...
You wanna be more than just Shizuku-tan?
Is that a serious question?
OMG, I have like 50 all-time fave characters!
What's the point of favorites, then?
This is such a hard decision.
I mean, I still wanna cosplay the heck out of Shizuku-tan.
But like, there are so many cosplays I wanna do,
and I only have one body to work with.
What's that face about?
Aw, look at that shy smile.
You know, I think you might be happier than you let on.
Uh, no, I, uh, I was just thinking about something.
Oh, yeah?
What?
Out with it.
Well, you know, it's...
Um, I know I'm not great yet,
but I'm looking forward to working with you again.
Mm-hmm, for sure.
We need a dress form.
I'm gonna go buy one.
It was kinda rough just winging it.
That sounds like a great idea.
Actually, I'll buy it for you.
I wonder if we can get one online.
Sweet, found one.
Here, check this guy out.
Looks like someone needs a nap.
Sleepy much?
Oh, yeah, I'm sorry.
Guess I'm pretty wiped.
I had so much fun, Gojo.
Thanks for an amazing day.
Actually, it seemed like everyone was having fun.
It was so insane.
All those people together in one spot,
doing what they loved.
The vibe was so hype.
I just ate it up.
That's my favorite thing.
Whether it's a hobby or a job or whatever,
I love being around people having fun doing what they love.
I can almost see them sparkle.
I can't wait to go to more events.
Holy crap, I didn't even take any pics with the other cosplayers.
I'm gonna go full paparazzi next time.
Like that Leo.
That was one cosplay I would have loved to have a shot with.
Leo from Seven BFs is so money.
How are they all so beautiful without a filter?
It's not fair.
You're right.
Kitagawa.
You looked so beautiful today.
No other word since then
could define the things most precious to me.
So I don't say beautiful or pretty
unless it comes from the heart.
you
Huh...
イタズラその一言つきゅんできたの
Ah これ以上期待しちゃだめ
今は二人で夢追いかけて
ピュワピュワ一途なハートが
ふわふわふわふわ
I can't believe it, but I can't believe it
I can't believe it, too
I'll be honest with you
So, please, please
I can't believe it, too
Na na na na na na na
Next time